Missing security requirements matters because healthcare applications often handle ePHI,
user identity, clinical workflows, patient portals, APIs, and integrations.
Teams should look for this issue in user-facing features, administrative tools,
background jobs, and service-to-service communication.
Weak workflows matters because healthcare applications often handle ePHI, user identity,
clinical workflows, patient portals, APIs, and integrations.
Teams should look for this issue in user-facing features, administrative tools,
background jobs, and service-to-service communication.
Unsafe architecture matters because healthcare applications often handle ePHI,
user identity, clinical workflows, patient portals, APIs, and integrations.
Teams should look for this issue in user-facing features, administrative tools,
background jobs, and service-to-service communication.
Lack of threat modeling matters because healthcare applications often handle ePHI,
user identity, clinical workflows, patient portals, APIs, and integrations.
Teams should look for this issue in user-facing features, administrative tools,
background jobs, and service-to-service communication.
Threat modeling Secure SDLC Security architecture reviews Selected HIPAA mappings for this
topic include Section 164.308(a)(1)(ii)(A) - Risk analysis;
Section 164.308(a)(1)(ii)(B) - Risk management; Section 164.308(a)(8) - Evaluation.